FURKAN GÜLER

Full-stack Developer

Due to a long-time interest in the field and against the backdrop of my higher education, I started Software Development training in 2019 and have since been improving myself in the fields of Full-stack Web and Desktop for the last 3 years. Able to design and develop Web apps, build APIs and manage databases.

Mersin, Türkiye +905435142290

furkang2k20@outlook.com linkedin.com/in/furkan-glr github.com/mystictide

About

Languages

English *advanced*Turkish *native*

Military Service Completed

Tech Stack

.NET & .NET Core

C#, JavaScript

Node.js, Express.js

React.js & React Redux

SASS/CSS, HTML5

 $SQL\ Server,\ PostgreSQL,\ MongoDB$

Docker, Ubuntu

Certificates

Programming in C# Certification

Developing ASP.NET MVC Web Applications Querying Microsoft SQL Server 2012/2014 Developing Microsoft Azure and Web Services Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3 MPP in Front-End Web Development

Projects

Cultured

A web app to find summarized information on a selection of cultural domains. A mini-Wikipedia of sorts

Trainer

A web app to help users find a library of exercises that target specific muscle groups

Tester

A web application that aims to challenge users with quizzes on a large and diverse amount of topics

Explore Spotify

A web app that offers track recommendations with users' favorite artists and tracks

Education

Management Information Systems

Anadolu University, Faculty of Open Education 2020 – Present

English Language and Literature

Akdeniz University, Faculty of Literature 2019 – 2020

Japanese Language and Literature

Erciyes University, Faculty of Literature 2017 – 2018

Experience

Freelance Web Developer

Jun 2022 – Present

Designed, developed and deployed a number of projects with the intent of building a stronger portfolio and experience using different tools and frameworks

Full-stack Web Developer

Başaran Akademi, Antalya Jan 2021 – Jun 2021

Rebuilt a static Website from the ground up and supplied it with a custom CMS

Built the core features of a Web app serving as a regional job listings database

Worked together with a small team of senior developers and designers

Full-stack Developer

KodEkibi, Antalya Jun 2020 – Jan 2021

Built a complex ERP software based on WinForms

Converted the desktop software into a Web app utilizing a Web API as the backend

Created and managed an SQL database

Built an internal interface to be used in future projects

Showcased the features of the app for potential customers